A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Communications, SG 2, Series 5 FA481
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Communications, 5
  - Publications, 5
    - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Chart Book - The Financing of Academic Health Centers, 1977 Sept. (Box 46, Folder 424)
    - New York Academy 0f Sciences - 180th Anniversary Charles Darwin Associates Annual Meeting and Dinner, 1997 September 25 (Box 46, Folder 425)
    - Association for Health Services Research - Conference, 1997 Sept., 1999 Aug. (Box 46, Folder 426)
    - Executive Summary - An Examination of Key Medicare Provisions in the Balanced Budget act of 1997, 1997 Sept.-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 427)
    - Health Affairs - Managed Care Performance - Is Quality of Care Better or Worse? Vol. 16, No. 5, 1997 Sept._oct. (Box 46, Folder 428)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Commission on Women's Health - In Their Own Words - Adolescent Girls Discuss Health and Health Care Issues and Survey, 1997 March - Nov. (Box 46, Folder 429)
    - Working Families at Risk - Coverage, Access, Costs, and Worries - Kaiser/Commonwealth 1997 National Survey of Health Insurance, 1997 June, Sept., Dec. (Box 46, Folder 430)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Harvard University - Fellowship in Minority Health Policy - Pamphlet, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 431)
    - Assessing a Foundations Performance - Executive Vice President's Report - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 432)
    - Common Concerns - In International Issues i Health Care System Reform - President's Message - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 433)
    - Assuring quality, Information, and Choice in Managed Care - Reprint - Inquiry, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 434)
    - Low-Income Working Families at Risk - Uninsured and Underserved - Reprint - Jouranl of Urban Health, 1998 March (Box 46, Folder 435)
    - Caring for tje Uninsured - The Urban Dilemma - Reprint - Journal od Urban Health, 1998 March (Box 46, Folder 436)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Survey of Health Care in New York City, 1998 March (Box 46, Folder 437)
    - The Improving Health Care Coverage and Affordability Series - Covering Uninsured Children and their Parents - Estimated Costs and Number of Newly Insured, 1998 July (Box 46, Folder 438)
    - The Improving Health Care Coverage and Affordability Series - State Subsidized Health Insurance Programs for Low-Income Residents' - Program Structure, Administration and Costs, 1998 April (Box 46, Folder 439)
    - The Improving Health Care Coverage and Affordability Series - Targeting Long-and Short-Term Gaps in Health Insurance, 1998 July (Box 46, Folder 440)
    - Policy Brief - assessing quality in Managed Care - Health Plan Reporting of Hedis Performance Measures, 1998 Sept. (Box 46, Folder 441)
    - When Employers Choose Health Plans - Do NCQA Accreditation and Hedis Data Count, 1998 Sept. (Box 46, Folder 442)
    - Health Care in New York City Program - Insuring the Children of New York City's Low - Income Families, 1998 Dec. (Box 47, Folder 443)
    - Medicare Beneficiaries - A Population at Risk - Kaiser/Commonwealth 1997 Survey of Medicare Beneficiaries, 1998 Dec. (Box 47, Folder 444)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Harkness Fellowships in Health Care, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 445)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 447, Folder 446)
    - Health and Aging in the 21st Century - President's Message - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 448)
    - Publications of the Commonwealth Fund, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 449)
    - Improving the Health of Adolescent Girls - Policy Report of the CWF Commission on Women's Health, 1999 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 450)
    - Demography is not Destiny - National Academy on an Aging Society, 1999 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 452, Folder 451)
    - Restucturing Medicare - Impacts on Beneficiaries - The Urban Institute, 1999 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 453)
    - Growth in Medicare Spending - What Will Beneficiaries Pay? - The Urban Institute, 1999 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 454, Folder 455)
    - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Patterns of Specialty Care - Academic Health Centers and th Patient Care Mission & Briefing Note, 1999 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 456)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 Jan. (Box 47, Folder 457)
    - Health Affairs - Future of Medicine Vol. 18, No. 1, 1999 Jan.-Feb. (Box 47, Folder 458)
    - Safety Net Hospitals - Essential Providers of Public Health and Specialty Services, 1999 Feb. (Box 48, Folder 459)
    - Should Medicare HMO Benifits Be Standardized?, 1999 Feb. (Box 48, Folder 460)
    - Employer - Sponsered Health Insurence - Implications for Minority Workers & News Release, 1999 Feb. (Box 48, Folder 461)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 Feb. (Box 48, Folder 462)
    - Medicaid Managed Care and Cultural Diversity in California & Briefing Note, 1999 Feb.- March (Box 48, Folder 463)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 March (Box 48, Folder 464)
    - Improving Lives Through Information - Reprint - Haelth Affairs, 1999 March-April (Box 48, Folder 465)
    - Tasf Force on Academic Health Centers - From Bench to Bedside - Preserving the Research Mission of Academic Health Centers & Issue Brief, 1999 March-April (Box 48, Folder 466)
    - Issue Brief - New Approches to Academic Health Center Affiliations - Public Hospital and the Department of Veteran Affairs, 1999 April (Box 48, Folder 467)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 April (Box 48, Folder 468)
    - Policy Brief - Community Health Centers in a Changing U. S. Health Care System, 1999 May (Box 48, Folder 469)
    - U. S. Minority Health - A Chart Book, 1999 May (Box 48, Folder 470)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Growth in Medicare Spending - What Will Beneficiaries Pay? & Briefing Note, 1999 May (Box 48, Folder 471)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Restructuring Medicare - Impacts on Beneficiaries, 1999 May (Box 48, Folder 472)
    - Women's Health - Current Trends and Issues, 1999 May (Box 48, Folder 473)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 May (Box 48, Folder 474)
    - Health Spending, Access and Outcomes - Trends in Industrialized Countries - Reprint - Health Affairs, 1999 May-June (Box 48, Folder 475)
    - The Cost of Health System Change - Public Discontent in Five Nations - Reprint - Health Affairs, 1999 May-June (Box 48, Folder 476)
    - Health Affairs - International Health Reform Vol. 18, No.3, 1999 May-June (Box 49, Folder 477)
    - Alliance for Health Reform - Financing Long - Term Care - Not a Phantom Menace - A Briefing on Trends and Policy for Now and Tomorrow, 1999 June (Box 49, Folder 478)
    - Risk Adjustment and Medicare, 1999 June (Box 49, Folder 479)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 July (Box 49, Folder 480)
    - Survey of Fund Audiences - Report to the Board of Directors, 1999 July 15 (Box 49, Folder 481)
    - Health Care in New York City Program - A New Opportunity to Provide Health Care Coverage for New York's Low - Income Families & Briefing Note, 1999 July (Box 49, Folder 483, Folder 482)
    - Policy Brief - The President's Proposed Long - Term Care Initiative - Background and Issues, 1999 July (Box 49, Folder 485, Folder 484)
    - Where are the Missing Elders? The Decline in Nursing Home Use, 1985-1995 - Reprint - Health Affairs, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 49, Folder 486)
    - Income Levels of Bad Debt and Free - Care - Patients in Massachisetts Hospitals - Reprint - Health Affairs, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 49, Folder 487)
    - Media Coverage and Clippings, 1999 Aug. (Box 49, Folder 488)
    - Issue Brief - Health Care in New York City - Understanding and Shaping Change, 1999 Sept. (Box 49, Folder 489)
    - Issue Brief - Long - Term Care in New York - Innovation in Care for Elderly and Disabled People, 1999 Sept. (Box 49, Folder 490)
    - Financing Long-Term Care in the Twenty-First Century - The Public and Private Roles & Briefing Note, 1999 Sept. (Box 49, Folder 491)
    - Can't Afford to Get Sick - A Reality for Millions of Working Americans - The Commonwealth Fund 1999 National Survey of Workers Health Insurance, 1999 Sept. (Box 49, Folder 492)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance for Working Americans - Can't Afford to Get Sick - A Reality for Millions of Working Americans, 1999 Sept. (Box 49, Folder 493)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 1999 Sept. (Box 49, Folder 494)
    - Managed Care in Three States - Experiences of Low - Income African Americans and Hispanics - Reprint Inquiry & Briefing Note, 1999, 2000 April (Box 49, Folder 495)
    - After the Bipartisan Commission - What Next for Medicare, 1999 Oct. (Box 49, Folder 496)
    - Media Coverage and Clippings, 1999 Oct. 19 (Box 49, Folder 497)
    - Media Coverage and Clippings, 1999 Oct. 29 (Box 49, Folder 499, Folder 498)
    - Media Coverage and Clippings, 1999 Nov. (Box 49, Folder 500, Box 50, Folder 501)
    - The Dependence of Safety NetbHospitals and Health Systems on the Medicare and Medicaid Disproportionate Share Hospital Payment Program and Briefing Note, 1999 Nov. (Box 50, Folder 502)
    - Contemporary Issues in Mentoring, 1999 Nov. (Box 50, Folder 503, Folder 504)
    - Models of Excellence - Innovative Programs for Young Children Age 0-3, 1999 Nov. (Box 50, Folder 505)
    - Health Affairs - Future of Health Insurance Vol. 18, No. 6, 1999 Nov.-Dec. (Box 50, Folder 506)
    - Job - Based Health Insurance, 1977-1998 - The Accidental System Under Scruting - Reprint - Health Affairs, 1999 Nov.-Dec. (Box 50, Folder 507)
    - Sponsor - A - Scholar - Long - Term Impacts of A Youth Mentoring Program on Student Performance & Briefing Note, 1999 Dec. (Box 50, Folder 508)
    - Health Care Policy - Report - The Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., 1999 Dec. - 2000 Feb. (Box 50, Folder 509)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Quarterly - A Digest of Current Work in Healthy Policy and Practice, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 510)
    - The Fund's Performance as a Grantmaker, 1992-1999 - Executive Vice President's Report - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 511)
    - Health Policy - Health Insurance Markets and Income Inequality - Findings From an International Health Policy Survey, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 512)
    - Selected Publications, 1999-2000 - Improving Health Insurance Coverage and Access to Care (Box 50, Folder 513)
    - Listening to Workers - Challenges for Employer Sponsored Coverage in the 21st Century, 2000 Jan. (Box 50, Folder 514)
    - Listening to Workers - Findings From the Commonwealth Fund 1999 National Survey of Worker's Health Insurance, 2000 Jan. (Box 51, Folder 515)
    - Risk for Midlife Americans - Getting Sick, Becoming Disabled, or Losing a Job and Health Coverage, 2000 Jan. (Box 51, Folder 516)
    - Discussion Paper - Reforming the Medicaid Disproportionate Share Hospital Program in the 1990's, 2000 Jan. (Box 51, Folder 517)
    - Issue Brief - A Vote of Confidence - Attitudes Toward Employer-Sponsered Health Insurance, 2000 Jan. (Box 51, Folder 518)
    - Issue Brief - Prescription Drug Costs for Medicare Beneficiaries - Coverage and Health Status Matter & News Release, 2000 Nan., Feb. 2 (Box 51, Folder 519)
    - Issue Brief - Assuring the Healthy Development of Young Children - Opportunities for States, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 520)
    - Trends in Specialized Surgical Proceedures at Teaching and Non Teaching Hospitals - Reprint - Health Affairs & Briefing Note, 2000 Jan.-Feb., April (Box 51, Folder 521)
    - National Medicaid Hedis Database/Benchmark Project & Briefing Note, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 522)
    - Five Boroughs, Common Problems - The Uninsured in New York City & News Release, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 523)
    - Working Without Benefits - The Health Insurance Crisis Confronting Hispanic Americans and News Release, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 524)
    - Working Without Benefits - The Health Insurance Crisis Confronting Hispanic Americans, 2000 March (Box 52, Folder 525)
    - Media Coverage - Health Stories, 2000 Feb.-March (Box 51, Folder 526)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 2000 March (Box 51, Folder 527)
    - Out of Touch - American Men and the Health Care System, 2000 March (Box 51, Folder 529, Folder 528)
    - Video Monitoring Services - Report, 2000 March 15 (Box 51, Folder 530)
    - Understanding Economic and Other Burdens of Terminal Illness - The Experience of Patients and Their Caregivers - Reprint - Annals of Internal Medicine, 2000 March 21 (Box 51, Folder 531)
    - Field Report - Task Force on the Role of WIC Centers and Small Business in Enrolling Uninsured Children in Medicaid and Child Health Plus, 2000 March (Box 51, Folder 532)
    - Field Report - Task Force on Using Community Groups and Student Volunteers to Enroll Uninsured Children in Medicaid and Child Health Plus, 2000 March (Box 51, Folder 533)
    - About Us - Quarterly Update - cmwf.org News, 2000 March (Box 51, Folder 534)
    - Drug Coverage and Drug Purchases by Medicare Beneficiaries with Hypertension - Reprint - Health Affairs & News Release, 2000 March-April (Box 51, Folder 535)
    - Media Coverage of the Fund Work, 2000 April-May (Box 51, Folder 536)
    - Field Report - Educating Medicaid Beneficiaries about Manage Care - Approuches in 13 Cities & News Release, 2000 May (Box 52, Folder 537)
    - Field Report - State Experience with Cost-Sharing - Mechanism in Children's Health Insurance Expansions, 2000 May (Box 51, Folder 538)
    - The Elderly's Experiences with Health Care in Five Nations - Findings From CWF 1999 International Health Policy Survey, 2000 May (Box 51, Folder 539)
    - About Us - Quarterly Update, 2000 May (Box 52, Folder 540)
    - Issue Brief - Equity In Health Care Across Five Nations - Summary Findings From an International Health Policy Survey, 2000 May (Box 52, Folder 541)
    - On Their Own - Young Adults Living Without Health Insurance & News Release, 2000 May (Box 52, Folder 542)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - An Assessment of The President's Proposal to Modernize and Strengthen Medicare, 2000 June (Box 52, Folder 543)
    - Malnutrition and Dehydration in Nursing Homes - Key Issues in Prevention and Treatment & News Release, 2000 June (Box 52, Folder 544)
    - Media Coverage - Video Monitoring Services, 2000 June-July (Box 52, Folder 545)
    - Counting on Medicare - Perspective and Concerns of Americans Ages 50-70 - Findings, 2000 July (Box 52, Folder 546)
    - Executive Summary - Counting on Medicare - Perspective and Concerns of Americans Ages 50-70, 2000 July (Box 52, Folder 547)
    - Health Care at the Cutting Edge - The Roll of Academic Health Centers in the Provision of Specialty Care, 2000 July (Box 52, Folder 548)
    - Media Coverage & Clips Video Monitoring Services, 2000 July-Sept. (Box 52, Folder 549)
    - Disparities in Health Insurance and Access to Care for Residents Across U. S. Cities - UCLA Center for Health Policy Research, 2000 Aug. (Box 52, Folder 550)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Early Implementation of Medicare+Choice in Four States - Cleveland, Los Angeles, New York, and Tampa - St. Petersburg - & Briefing Note, 2000 Aug. (Box 52, Folder 551)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Medicare+Choice in 2000 - Will Enrollees Spend More and Recieve Less?, & Briefing Note, 2000 Aug. (Box 52, Folder 552)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - What Do Medicare HMO Enrollees Spend Out-Of-Pocket & Briefing Note, 2000 Aug. (Box 52, Folder 553)
    - Background Report - Perspectives on PPO Performance Measurment From Consumers, PPO Lenders, and Employees, 2000 Sept. (Box 52, Folder 554)
    - The Rolls of Medicare and Medicaid in Financing - Health and Long-Term Care for Low-Income Seniors - A Chart Book on Medicare - Medicaid Enrollees in Four States, 2000 May (Box 53, Folder 555)
    - Healthy Steps for Young Children - Appraisals of Parenting, Parent-Child Interactions, Parenting Styles, and Children - Ab Annotated Bibliography, 2000 Sept. (Box 53, Folder 556)
    - Issue Brief - Living Longer, Staying Well - Promoting Good Health for Older Women, 2000 Sept. (Box 53, Folder 557)
    - Field Report - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Managing Academic Health Centers - Meeting the Challenges of the New Health Care World, 2000 Oct. (Box 53, Folder 558)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 2000 Oct. (Box 53, Folder 559)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - ERISA and State Health Care Access Initiatives - Opportunities and Obstacles, 2000 Oct. (Box 53, Folder 561, Folder 560)
    - Emergency Department Use - The New York Story, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 562)
    - Emergency Department Use in New York City - A Substitute for Promary Care?, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 563)
    - Emergency Department Use in New York City - A Survey of Bronx Patients, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 564)
    - Program on Health Care Quality Improvement - Effective Clinical Practices in Managed Care - Findings From Ten Case Studies, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 565)
    - Program on Health Care Quality Improvement - Getting Behind the Numbers - Understanding Patients Assessments of Managed Care, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 566)
    - Program on Health Care Quality Improvement - Growth in Medicare and Out-Of-Pocket Spending - Impact on Vulnerable Beneficiaries, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 567)
    - Recent Grants - Awarded by the Board of Directors, 2000 April, July, Nov. (Box 53, Folder 568)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - State and Local Initiatives to Enhance Health Coverage for the Working Uninsured, 2000 Nov. (Box 53, Folder 569)
    - Media Coverage & Clips, 2000 Dec. (Box 53, Folder 570)
    - Media Coverage - National Journal - Health Line, 2000 Dec. (Box 53, Folder 571)
    - Policy Brief - Designing a Medicare Drug Benefit - Whose Need Will Be Met?, 2000 Dec. (Box 53, Folder 572)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Barriers to Health Coverage for Hispanic Workers - Focus Group Findings, 2000 Dec. (Box 53, Folder 573)
    - Assessing the Value of Presidential Discretionary Grants - Executive Vice President's Report - Annual Report, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 574)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Annual Report, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 575)
    - Health Care in New York City - Creating a Seamless Health Insurance System for New York's Children, 2001 Feb. (Box 53, Folder 576)
    - Health Care in New York City - Expanding Access to Health Insurance Coverage for Low-Income Immigrants in New York State, 2001 March (Box 53, Folder 577)
    - Early Effects of the Healthy Steps for Young Children Program - American Medical Association, 2001 April (Box 53, Folder 578)
    - Status of Clinical Research in Academic Health Centers - Views From the Research Leadership - Ameriacan Medical Association, 2001 Aug. (Box 53, Folder 579)
    - The Journal of the American Medical Association - Preparedness for Clinical Practice & Brief Note, 2001 Sept. 5, Dec. (Box 54, Folder 580)
    - National and Local Factors Driving Health Plan Withdrawals From Medicare+Choice, 2001 Oct. (Box 53, Folder 582, Folder 581)
    - Restoring Choice to Medicare+Choice - The Importance of Standardizing Health Plan Benefit Packages, 2001 Oct. (Box 53, Folder 584, Folder 583)
    - Picker-Commonwealth Program on Quality of Care for Elders - Coordinating Care for the Elderly - A Case Study of a Medicaid Long-Term Care Capitation Program in New York, 2001 Oct. (Box 54, Folder 585)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Business Initiatives to Expand Health Coverage for Workers in Small Firms Vol. 1, Overview and Lessons Learned, 2001 Oct. (Box 54, Folder 586)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - How the Slowing U. S. Economy Threstens Employer-Based Health Insurance, 2001 Nov. (Box 54, Folder 587, Folder 588)
    - Health Care in New York City - Healthy New York - Making Insurance Affordable for Low-Income Workers, 2001 Nov. (Box 54, Folder 589)
    - Health Care in New York City - Implementing New York's Family Health Plus Program - Lessons From the States, 2001 Nov. (Box 54, Folder 590)
    - In the Literature - Nursing Home Regulation - Lessons Learned for Reform, 2001 Nov.-Dec. (Box 54, Folder 591)
    - Experience of Working-Age Adults in the Individual Insurance Market, 2001 Dec. (Box 54, Folder 592)
    - Maintaining Health Insurance During Recession - Likely COBRA Eligibility, 2001 Dec. (Box 54, Folder 593)
    - Primary Care Services Promoting Optimal Child Development FRom Birth to Age 3 Years - American Medical Assiciation, 2001 Dec. (Box 54, Folder 594)
    - Security Matters - How Instability in Health Insurance Puts U. S. Workers at Risk, 2001Dec., 2002 Jan.28 (Box 54, Folder 595)
    - The Commonwealth Fund Quarterly - A Digest of Current Work in Health Policy and Practice, 2001-2003 (Box 54, Folder 596)
    - Field Report - Program on Health Care Quality Improvement - Accessing Physician Information on the Internet, 2002 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 597)
    - Field Report - Program on Medicare's Future - Physicians Withdrawals - A Major Source of Instability in the Medicare+Choice Program, 2002 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 598)
    - Issue Brief - Drug Coverage for Medicare Beneficiaries - Why Protection May Be in Jeopardy, 2002 Jan. (Box 54, Folder 599)
    - Field Report - Health Care in New York City - Lessons From a Small Business Insurance Demonstration Project & Briefing Note, 2002 Feb. (Box 54, Folder 600)
    - Field Report - Program on Medicare'se - Out-Of-Pocket Health Care Expenses for Medicare HMO Beneficiaries - Estamates by Health Status, 1999-2001, 2002 Feb. (Box 55, Folder 601)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Medicare+Choice 1999-2001 - An Analysis of Managed Care Plan Withdrawals and Trends in Benefits and Premiums, 2002 Feb. (Box 55, Folder 602)
    - Diverse Communities, Common Concerns Assessing Health Care Quality for Minority Americans, 2002 March (Box 55, Folder 603)
    - Field Report - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - E-Health Options for Business - Evaluationg the Choices, 2002 March (Box 55, Folder 604)
    - In the Literature - Racial Disparities in Quality of Care for Enrollees in Medicare Managed Care, 2002 March 13 (Box 55, Folder 605)
    - In the Literature - Individual Insurance - How Much Financial Protection Does It Provide, 2002 April 17 (Box 55, Folder 606)
    - Program on Health Care Quality Improvement - Room for Improvement - Patients Report on the Quality of Their Health Care, 2002 April (Box 55, Folder 607)
    - Training Tomorrow's Doctors - The Medical Education Mission of Academic Health Centers & Briefing Note, 2002 April-June (Box 55, Folder 610, Folder 609, Folder 608)
    - Field Report - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations - Providing Language Interpretation Services in Health Care Settings - Examples From the Field, 2002 May (Box 55, Folder 611)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Are Tax Credits Alone the Solution to Affordable Health Insurance? - Comparing Individual and Group Insurance Cost in 7 U. S. Markets, 2002 May (Box 55, Folder 612, Folder 613)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - State Pharmacy Assistance Programs - Approaches to Program Design, 2002 May (Box 55, Folder 615, Folder 614)
    - Issue Brief - Bare - Bones Health Plans - Are They Worth the Money?, 2002 May (Box 55, Folder 616)
    - In the Literature - Do Enrollees in "Look - Alike" Medicaid and SCHIP Programs Really Look Alike?, 2002 May-June (Box 55, Folder 617)
    - In the Literature - Eliminating Racial/Ethnic Disparities in Health Care - Can Health Plans Generate Reports?, 2002 May-June (Box 55, Folder 618)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Family Out - Of - Pocket Spending for Health Services - A Continuing Source of Financial Insecurity, 2002 June (Box 55, Folder 620, Folder 619)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - 2002 Annual Report - Ended, 2002 June 30 (Box 55, Folder 621)